Inventory of the Elisabeth Burgos-Debray papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Régis Debray File, 1967-1971
  - Correspondence, 1967-1971
    - Debray, Georges and Janine Alexandre-Debray, 1967-1971
      - Lioncourt, Thérèse, 1968 (Box-folder 13: 43)
      - Marin, Jean, 1967 (Box-folder 13: 44)
      - Maspero, François, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 13: 45)
      - Maurer, José Clemente, 1967 (Box-folder 13: 46)
      - Monde (Jacques Fauvet), 1967-1970 (Box-folder 13: 47)
      - Neruda, Pablo, 1970 (Box-folder 13: 48)
      - Ovando Candio, Alfredo, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 13: 49)
      - Paris Match, 1967 (Box-folder 13: 50)
      - Payan, Jacqueline, 1967 (Box-folder 13: 51)
      - Pinet, Georges, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 13: 52)
      - Pompidou, Georges, 1967 (Box-folder 13: 53)
      - Ponchardier, Dominique, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 13: 54)
      - Ray, Michèle, 1969 (Box-folder 13: 55)
      - Regnault, Odile-Catherine, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 13: 56)
      - Revueltas, Naty, 1970 (Box-folder 13: 57)
      - Rivals, Pédro, 1969 (Box-folder 13: 58)
      - Robin, Jean, 1967 (Box-folder 13: 59)
      - Rojo, Ricardo, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 13: 60)
      - Slim, Mohsen, 1969 (Box-folder 14: 1)
      - Suarez Guzman, Hugo, 1967 (Box-folder 14: 2)
      - Thuillier, Marcel, 1969 (Box-folder 14: 3)
      - Vallon, Louis, 1969 (Box-folder 14: 4)
      - Vezinat, Yolande, 1967 (Box-folder 14: 5)
      - Vogel, Paul Ignaz, 1967 (Box-folder 14: 6)
      - Vollenweider, Ernest-François, 1968 (Box-folder 14: 7)
    - Debray, Régis, 1967-1968
      - Collective letters of support, 1968 (Box-folder 14: 8)
      - Bronner, Alain, 1968 (Box-folder 14: 9)
      - Flores, Walter, 1967 (Box-folder 14: 10)
      - Gaulle, Charles de, 1967 (Box-folder 14: 11)
      - Novillo, Raul, 1967 (Box-folder 14: 12)
  - Credentials issued to Elisabeth Burgos-Debray by the Bolivian military, authorizing visits to see Régis Debray in Camiri prison, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 14: 13)
  - Declarations, 1967-1969
    - Burgos-Debray, Elisabeth, 1969 (Box-folder 14: 14)
    - Debray, Georges, 1967 (Box-folder 14: 15)
    - Debray, Régis, 1967 (Box-folder 14: 16)
    - Maspero, François, 1967 (Box-folder 14: 17)
  - Demand for writ of habeas corpus made on behalf of Régis Debray, 1967 (Box-folder 14: 18)
  - Diplomatic pass issued to Elisabeth Burgos-Debray by the French government, 1967 (Box-folder 14: 19)
  - Journal of Pédro Rivals, describing events in Bolivia, 1968-1970
    - 1968 (Box-folder 14: 20)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 14: 21)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 14: 22)
  - List of books and recordings requested by Régis Debray during his imprisonment, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 14: 23)
  - List of signatories to a petition demanding the release of Régis Debray, 1969 (Box-folder 14: 24)
  - Notebook containing diary entries made by Georges Debray during the trial of Régis Debray, 1967 (Box-folder 14: 25)
  - Petition for amnesty of Régis Debray made by his lawyer, Georges Pinet, 1970 (Box-folder 14: 26)
  - Press conference materials, 1967
    - Correspondence with journalists, 1967 (Box-folder 14: 27)
    - Statements issued to the press by Georges Debray and Janine Alexandre-Debray, 1967 (Box-folder 14: 28)
    - Summary of press conference given by Georges Debray, 1967 July 15 (Box-folder 14: 29)
  - Proposals, 1967-1970
    - Escape plan, 1970 (Box-folder 14: 30)
    - Prisoner exchange, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 14: 31-32)
  - Transcript of interview with Régis Debray, 1969 December 25 (Box-folder 14: 33)
  - Transcript of argument made by defense lawyer Raúl Novillo during the sentencing phase of Régis Debray's trial, 1967 (Box-folder 14: 34)
- Subject File, 1967-1993
  Contains clippings and correspondence, arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Bolivia--Politics and government, 1967-1970
    - 1967 (Box-folder 15: 1-2)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 15: 3)
  - Cardoso Villavicencio, Orlando, 1988 (Box-folder 15: 4)
  - Chile--Politics and government, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 15: 5)
  - Cuba--Politics and government, 1968-1989 (Box-folder 15: 6)
  - Guevara, Ernesto "Che", 1967-1969 (Box-folder 15: 7)
  - Menchú, Rigoberta, 1982-1993 (Box-folder 15: 8)
  - Montoneros, 1976 (Box-folder 15: 9)
  - Seville Exposition, 1989 (Box-folder 15: 10)
- Photographs, 1920-1988
  Contains prints arranged by subject.
  - Burgos-Debray, Elisabeth, 1970-1988
    - With Fidel Castro, Havana, Cuba, 1970 (Box-folder 15: 11)
    - With Rigoberta Menchú, Paris, France, 1982 (Box-folder 15: 12-13)
    - With Fidel Castro, Oswaldo Guayasamin, and Danielle Mitterrand, Quito, Ecuador, 1988 (Box-folder 15: 14)
  - Alexandre-Debray, Janine, Havana, Cuba, 1970 (Box-folder 15: 15)
  - Debray, Georges, 1920 (Box-folder 15: 16)
  - Solis, Marta, 1983 (Box-folder 15: 17)
- Printed Matter, 1966-1999
  Contains monographs and two numbers of a serial issue, arranged by physical form.
  - Monographs, 1966-1999
    - Burgos-Debray, Elisabeth with Rigoberta Menchú, Me llamo Rigoberta Menchú y así me nació la conciencia, 1983-1999
      - Spanish editions, 1992, 1998 (Box-folder 16: 1-2)
      - French translation, 1992 (Box-folder 16: 3)
      - English translation, 1986 (Box-folder 16: 4)
      - Danish translation, 1985 (Box-folder 16: 5)
      - Finnish translation, 1990 (Box-folder 16: 6-7)
      - Japanese translation, 1987 (Box-folder 16: 8)
      - Dutch translation, 1983, 1993 (Box-folder 17: 1-2)
      - German translation, 1992 (Box-folder 17: 3)
      - Italian translation, 1987, 1999 (Box-folder 17: 4-5)
    - Other monographs, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 17: 6-8)
  - Serial issue, Paradiso, 1994 July/August-September/October (Box-folder 17: 9-10)
- Sound Recordings, 1970-2002
  Contains interviews recorded on compact sound cassettes, micro sound cassettes, and sound tape reels, arranged by physical form.
  - Compact sound cassettes, 1982-1998
    - Interviews of Rigoberta Menchú conducted by Elisabeth Burgos-Debray, 1982 January 7-9, undated (Reading room workstation)
      Access
      Use copy reference numbers: 2001c89_a_0005931 through 5934, 5937, 5938, 5965, 5966, 5969, 5970, 5974, 5975, 5980 through 5983
      - Original recordings, 1982 January 7-9, undated
        Scope and Content note
        Box/Tape 18: 1-16
      - Duplicates, 1982
        Box/Tape 18: 17-32
    - Interview of Rigoberta Menchú conducted by Arturo Taracena Arriola, 1982 (Reading room workstation)
      Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0006613 (?)
      - Original recording, 1982
        Box/Tape 19: 1
      - Duplicate, 1982
        Box/Tape 19: 2
    - "Torture Guatemala" interviews of Rigoberta Menchú conducted by Elisabeth Burgos-Debray and others, 1982 (Reading room workstation)
      Use copy reference numbers: 2001c89_a_0003136, 3150, 3200, 3201, 6612 (?)
      Box/Tape 19: 3-9
    - Interviews conducted by Elisabeth Burgos-Debray, 1996-1998
      - Alarcón Ramirez, Daniel "Benigno,", 1996-1997
        - 1996 July 26 (Reading room workstation)
          Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0006608
          Box/Tape 19: 10-11
        - 1996 July 27 (Reading room workstation)
          Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0006609 through 6611
          Box/Tape 19: 12-14
      - Masetti, Jorge, 1997-1998
        - 1997 April 26 (Reading room workstation)
          Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0006606 through 6607
          Box/Tape 19: 15-16
        - 1998 November 23 (Reading room workstation)
          Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0006604 through 6605
          Box/Tape 19: 17-18
  - Micro sound cassettes containing interviews conducted by Elisabeth Burgos-Debray, 1997-2002
    - Venezuela, 1997-2002
      - Pérez Marcano, Héctor, 1997-1998
        - 1997 December 15 (Reading room workstation)
          Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0006690
          Box/Tape 20: 1-3
        - 1998 January 7 (Reading room workstation)
          Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0006692
          Box/Tape 20: 4
      - Bravo, Douglas, 1997-2000
        - 1997 December 19 (Reading room workstation)
          Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0006695
          Box/Tape 20: 5-7
        - 1998 January 5-6 (Reading room workstation)
          Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0006702
          Box/Tape 20: 8
        - 1998 January 5 (Reading room workstation)
          Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0006708
          Box/Tape 20: 9
        - 2000 December 22 (Reading room workstation)
          Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0006720
          Box/Tape 20: 10
      - Duno, Pedro, 1997 December 5-7 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference numbers: 2001c89_a_0006735 through 6737, 6742
        Box/Tape 20: 11-14
      - Márquez, Pompeyo, 1998 January 14, 16, June 1 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference numbers: 2001c89_a_0006746, 6748
        Box/Tape 20: 15-16
      - Petkoff, Teodoro, 1998 February 3 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007079
        Box/Tape 20: 17
      - Martín, Américo, 2002 December 22 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007082
        Box/Tape 20: 18
      - García Ponce, Guillermo, 1998 January 15 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007085
        Box/Tape 20: 19-20
      - Trejo, Hugo, 1998 January 13 undated (Reading room workstation)
        The undated recording sounds like it was conducted by telephone. Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007104, 7116
        Box/Tape 20: 21-22
      - Rigores, Bernardo, 1998 January 20 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007117
        Box/Tape 20: 23-24
      - Betancourt, Camilo, 1998 January 19 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007126
        Box/Tape 20: 25
      - Perez Marcano, Marelis, 1998 January 21 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007135
        Box/Tape 20: 26
      - Borjes, Luís, 1998 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007147
        Box/Tape 20: 27
      - Pérez, Carlos Andrés (side A) and Julio Escalona (side B), 1998 January 12 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007149
        Box/Tape 20: 28
      - Escalona, Julio, 1998 January 12 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007153
        Box/Tape 20: 29
      - Colmenarez, Cristóbal, 1997 December 29 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007154
        Box/Tape 20: 30
      - Zago, Angela, 1997 December 9 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007157
        Box/Tape 20: 31
      - Arguedas, Antonio, 1998 March 13 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference numbers: 2001c89_a_0007387, 7408, 7418
        Box/Tape 20: 32-34
    - Bolivia and Peru, 1998
      - Castillo, José "Paco" (side A) and Antonio Arguedas (side B), 1998 March 13 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007423
        Box/Tape 20: 35
      - Castillo, José "Paco,", 1998 March 13 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007430
        Box/Tape 20: 36
      - Sánchez, Rubén, 1998 January 13 - February 13 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007159
        Box/Tape 20: 37
        Sanchez se reunia con el Chato durante el gobierno de Torres para que frente a una amenaza de golpe pudiera haber una reacción. Entra oficialmente al ELN luego de ir al exilio en Perú. Los cubanos en Lima me relacionaron con del mir de chile, me dieron un departamento para que viva en chile, 19 piso, vitacura, montoneros, erp.
        Actividad muy estrecha con el ERP. Un simpatía reciproca con Santucho. La relacion que tenía con los otros se dilató pero con el ERP se fortaleció. Producto de esa relacion recibimos dinero del ERP para el ELN.
        Incluso el general Torres tuvo una relación con el ERP. "Nosotros, los argentinos, quisieramos tener la suerte que tienen los bolivianos de tener un general con las características de él" le dijo Santucho. No era asi. No era un militante mas del ELN. Yo estaba con todas las organizaciones revolucionarias. Con Regis también.
        Los del ERP me permitían asistir a sus ampliados.
        Torres tuvo una sola reunión con el ERP. Con Santucho y el gringo.
        A Torres lo mataron porque era un lider.
        Entre el 75 y el 78 yo trabajo como ALIN
        Debray trajo 100.000 dolares de lo que habíamos recaudado en Europa. Yo no quise recibirlo porque el FRA ya estaba dividido.
      - Zannier, Victor, 1998 February 10-15 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007433
        Box/Tape 20: 38-39
      - Sánchez, Gustavo, 1998 November 2 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007855
        Box/Tape 20: 40
        Entrevista al periodista Gustavo Sanchez (hermano de Ruben Sanchez). 2/11/98.
        Información relativa a la captura y liberación de Debray.
        Hay dos uruguayos que mataron en Caimiri. Sanchez se reunia con el Chato durante el gobierno de Torres para que ffrente a una amenaza de golpe pudiera haber una reacción. Entra oficialmente al ELN luego de ir al exilio en Perú. Los cubanos en Lima me relacionaron con del mir de chile, me dieron un departamento para que viva en chile, 19 piso, vitacura, montoneros, erp.
        Sanchez se reunia con el Chato durante el gobierno de Torres para que ffrente a una amenaza de golpe pudiera haber una reacción. Entra oficialmente al ELN luego de ir al exilio en Perú. Los cubanos en Lima me relacionaron con del mir de chile, me dieron un departamento para que viva en chile, 19 piso, vitacura, montoneros, erp.
      - Reyes, Simón, 1998 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007856
        Box/Tape 20: 41
      - Vásquez, Humberto, 1998 February 18 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007867
        Box/Tape 20: 42
      - Vásquez, Humberto (side A) and Gary Prado (side B), 1998 February 18-19 (Reading room workstation)
        Box/Tape 20: 43
      - Chávez, Mario "Lagunillero,", 1998 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007890
        Box/Tape 20: 44
      - Vásquez, Humberto (side A) and Juan Lechín Oquendo (side B), 1998 February 18-24 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007895
        Box/Tape 20: 45
      - Quezada, Marcelo, 1998 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007909
        Box/Tape 20: 46
      - Quezada, Marcelo (side A) and Héctor B!jar (side B), 1998 March 20-25 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007911
        Box/Tape 20: 47
      - Béjar, Héctor (side A) and Julio Dagnino (side B), 1998 March 25 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007920
        Box/Tape 20: 48
      - Dagnino, Julio, 1998 March 25 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007933
        Box/Tape 20: 49
    - Guatemala, 1998-1999
      - Ramirez, Ricardo, 1998 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007935
        Box/Tape 20: 50
      - Porras Castejón, Gustavo, 1999 March 18 (Reading room workstation)
        Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0007941
        Box/Tape 20: 51
  - Sound tape reels, 1970
    - Two 1/4-inch reels containing recordings relating to the trial and imprisonment of Régis Debray in Bolivia, 1970 (Reading room workstation)
      Use copy reference numbers: 2001c89_a_0006688 through 6689
      Box/Tape 20: 52-53
    - One 1/4-inch reel containing a recording of an unknown interview, 1970 (Reading room workstation)
      Use copy reference number: 2001c89_a_0006686
      Box/Tape 20: 54. In French.
- Videorecordings, 1983-2007
  Contains interviews recorded on digital videocassettes and a documentary recorded on VHS videocassettes, arranged by physical form.
  - Digital videocassettes containing interviews conducted by Elisabeth Burgos-Debray, 2003-2007
    - Cuban exiles, 2003-2004
      - Fernández, Lino and Emilita Luzanaya, 2003 (Box-tape 21: 1-2)
      - Fernández, Lino
        - 2003 (Box-tape 21: 3-5)
        - 2004 (Box-tape 21: 6-7)
      - Fernández, Lino and Ricardo Bofill, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 8)
      - Bofill, Ricardo, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 9-10)
      - Bofill, Ricardo and Angel Pardo, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 11)
      - Bringas, Generoso, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 12-13)
      - Iriondo, Sylvia G., 2004 (Box-tape 21: 14)
      - Lugo, Maritza, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 15)
      - Guzmán, José, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 16-18)
      - Otero Estrada, José, 2003 (Box-tape 21: 19-20)
      - Denis, Xavier, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 21-22)
      - Gutiérrez, Rafael, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 23-25)
      - Albertini, José Antonio, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 26-27)
      - Rivera, Agapito, 2003 (Box-tape 21: 28-30)
      - González, Teodoro, 2003 (Box-tape 21: 31-32)
      - Acosta, Rigoberto, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 33)
      - Hernández Vera, José, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 34)
      - Guzmán, José, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 35)
      - Esquivel, Rolando and Eduardo Martínez, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 36)
      - Esquivel, Rolando, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 37)
      - Talavera, Paco, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 38)
      - Portuondo, Jorge, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 39)
      - Montes de Oca, Juan Antonio, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 40)
      - Zayas-Bazán, Eduardo, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 41)
      - Nodarse, Olga, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 42-43)
      - Nodarse, Olga and Lino Fernández, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 44)
      - Basulto, José, 2003 (Box-tape 21: 45-46)
      - Prendes, Alvaro, 2004 (Box-tape 21: 47-48)
      - "Escenas de calle en Miami,", 2004 (Box-tape 21: 49)
      - "Reunón de ex-presos politicos,", 2004 (Box-tape 21: 50-51)
      - "Fiesta cubana en casa de Ramón Chao,", 2004 (Box-tape 21: 52)
      - "Fiesta y entrevista,", 2004 (Box-tape 21: 53)
      - "Asamblea Nacionale (Paris),", 2004 (Box-tape 21: 54)
      - "Manifestación,", 2004 (Box-tape 22: 1)
      - Díaz Rodríguez, Ernesto, 2004 (Box-tape 22: 2)
      - Chanes de Armas, Mario, 2003 (Box-tape 22: 3-4)
      - Simeón, Roberto, 2004 (Box-tape 22: 5-6)
      - Simeón, Roberto and Alvaro Prendes, 2004 (Box-tape 22: 7)
      - Corzo, Pedro, 2003 (Box-tape 22: 8-9)
      - Fernández, Carlos, 2004 (Box-tape 22: 10)
    - Venezuela, 2007
      - Poleo, Rafael, 2007 (Box-tape 22: 11-12)
      - "Coloquio autonomía universitaria,", 2007 (Box-tape 22: 13-15)
      - "Almuerzo en el Tennis Club de Caracas,", 2007 (Box-tape 22: 16-18)
      - "Conferencia Universidad Central,", 2007 (Box-tape 22: 19-20)
      - Asociación civil Súmate, 2007 (Box-tape 22: 21-22)
      - Petkoff, Teodoro, 2007 (Box-tape 22: 23-25)
      - Goicoechea, Yon, Pompeyo Márquez, and Américo Gregorio Martín Estaba, 2007 (Box-tape 22: 26-28)
      - "Estudiantes en Valencia,", 2007 (Box-tape 22: 29-30)
      - "Estudiantes en Caracas,", 2007 (Box-tape 22: 31-32)
      - Bottome, Peter, 2007 (Box-tape 22: 33-34)
    - Peru, 2004
      - Humala, Ollanta, 2004 (Box-tape 22: 35-36)
  - Videocassettes, 1983
    - "Pourquoi ils nous tuent?,", 1983 (Reading room workstation)
      Use copy reference number: 2001c89_v_0005914
      Documentary by Elisabeth Burgos [Elisabeth Burgos-Debray] and Isidro Romero. Color and black and white; sound.
      - VHS (PAL) videocassette, 1983
        Box/Tape 23: 1
      - VHS (SECAM) videocassette, 1983
        Box/Tape 23: 2
- Additional Sound Recordings, 1980-2001
  Compact sound cassettes containing interviews conducted by Elisabeth Burgos-Debray.
  - Venezuela, 1997-1999
    - Rigores, Bernardo, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 1 - 3)
    - Zago, Angela, 1997 (Box-tape 24: 4)
    - Colmenarez, Cristóbal, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 5)
    - Chávez, Hugo, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 6)
    - Petkoff, Teodoro, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 7)
    - Duno, Pedro, 1997 (Box-tape 24: 8)
  - Guatemala, 1999-2000
    - Castejón, Gustavo Porras, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 9 - 10)
    - Gramajo, Héctor, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 11)
    - Asturias, Rodrigo, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 12)
    - Montes, César, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 13)
    - Montes, César and Frank La Rue, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 14)
    - Carmen, Maria del, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 15)
    - Monsantos, Pablo, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 16 - 17)
    - Pellecer, Carlos Manuel, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 18)
    - Balconi, Julio, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 19)
    - Spiegler, Otto, 2000 (Box-tape 24: 20)
  - Argentina, 1999
    - Mattini, Luís (Box-tape 24: 21 - 22)
  - Mexico, 1999
    - Castañeda, Salvador, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 23)
  - Bolivia, 199-2001
    - Monje, Mario, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 24-27)
    - Claure, Hilario, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 28-29)
    - Quintana, Juan (Box-tape 24: 30)
    - Kolle, Jorge, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 31)
    - Zannier, Víctor, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 32-33)
    - Forti, Liber, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 34)
    - Sánchez, Ruben, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 35)
    - Crespo, Alberto, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 36)
    - Pareja, Walter, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 37)
    - Prado, Gary, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 38)
    - Dagnino, Julio, 1999 (Box-tape 24: 39-40)
    - Debray, Régis, 2001 (Box-tape 24: 41)
  - Cuba (includes Cuban exiles), 1999-2001
    - Chanes de Armas, Mario, 2001 (Box-tape 24: 42)
    - Chanes de Armas, Mario, 2001 (Box-tape 25: 1)
    - Corzo, Pedro, 1999 (Box-tape 25: 2)
    - García Buchaca, Edith, 2001 (Box-tape 25: 3-5)
    - Peñalver, Eusebio, 2001 (Box-tape 25: 6-7)
    - Salabarria, Mario, 1999 (Box-tape 25: 8)
    - Gutíerrez Menoyo, Eloy, 2001 (Box-tape 25: 9)
    - Matos, Huber, 2001 (Box-tape 25: 10)
  - Colombia, 1999
    - Arias Cabrales, Jesús (Box-tape 25: 11-12)
    - Ruiz Novoa, Alberto (side A) and Jésus Arias Cabrales (side B) (Box-tape 25: 13)
    - Valencia Tovar, Álvaro (Box-tape 25: 14-15)
    - Bedoya Pizarro, Harold (Box-tape 25: 16)
    - Villamarín Pulido, Luis Alberto (Box-tape 25: 17-19)
    - Pataquiva, Germán (Box-tape 25: 20-21)
    - Clavijo, Adolfo (Box-tape 25: 22)
    - Rios, Iván (Box-tape 25: 23)
    - Rios, Iván and Simón Trinidad (Box-tape 25: 24-25)
  - Peru, 1999
    - Blanco, Hugo (Box-tape 25: 26-27)
    - Blanco, Hugo and Miguel Ballón (side A), and Alberto Crespo (side B) (Box-tape 25: 28)
    - Blanco, Hugo (side A) and Estenio Pacheco (side B) (Box-tape 25: 29)
    - Saúl (Sendero Luminoso) (Box-tape 25: 30)
    - Jesús (Sendero Luminoso) (Box-tape 25: 31)
    - Pacheco, Doctor (Box-tape 25: 32)
  - Cuban women, 1980-1988
    - Santamaria, Haydée, Celia Hart, and Marta Solis, 1980 (Box-tape 25: 33)
    - Santamaria, Haydée, 1988 (Box-tape 25: 34)
    - Menendez Capote, Renée, 1988 (Box-tape 25: 35)
    - Oliver Labra, Carilda, 1988 (Box-tape 25: 36)
    - Loynaz, Dulce María, 1988 (Box-tape 25: 37)
    - Valdés, Zoe, 1988 (Box-tape 25: 38-41)
    - Fonseca, Nelia Rosa, 1988 (Box-tape 25: 42)
    - Llerena, Edith, 1988 (Box-tape 26: 1)
    - Véliz, Esther, 1988 (Box-tape 26: 2)
    - Revuelta, Nati, 1988 (Box-tape 26: 3)
    - Ruiz Prada, Niurka Maria and Vilma Salinas, 1988 (Box-tape 26: 4)
    - Véliz, Esther and Gloria de Dios, 1988 (Box-tape 26: 5)
    - Ruiz Prada, Niurka Maria, 1988 (Box-tape 26: 6)
    - Salinas, Vilma, 1988 (Box-tape 26: 7)
    - Torres, Dora and Rosa, 1988 (Box-tape 26: 8)
- CLOSED (Box 27)